Minh Quan Dao

Curriculum Vitae

Contact Information

Email: kevinquandao10@gmail.com

RESEARCH INTEREST

My research interest is generative model and its applications. I'm focusing on how to apply generative model to learn uncertainty from other supervised tasks such as segmentation/saliency detection. Besides, I'm also interested in contrastive representation learning and its application to do few-shot learning.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science

2018-2021

Monash University

EXPERIENCE

VinBigData 3/2021 - 3/2022

Bioplatform Project: In this project, I was a full stack developer who build a website (like Kaggle) which allows users to manage and submit biostatistic model.

University of Sydney

12/2021 - 2/2022

Motion Capture Analysis: In this summer research project, I'm doing research under supervision of professor Zhiyong Wang and his postdoc Kun Hu. In this project, we investigate cross-modal learning to generate beatsaber map (VR game) from music input. Currently, this is my side project as research affiliate at University of Sydney.

VinAI Research 8/2022 - Now

VinAI Residency: A full-time research internship at VinAI in Computer Vision team. In VinAI, I'm currently doing research on diffusion model and other generative models such as EBM, GAN and VAE.

HONORS, AWARDS

Second prize in VMO 2017 (Vietnam Mathematic Olympiad): I was ranked about 40 among more than 500 selective math gifted students from all province in Vietnam

SCHOLARSHIP

Sydney Research Summer Scholarship

2021

University of Sydney

Sydney

This scholarship is selected and awarded to students who engage in short-time research period at University of Sydney

SKILL

- Experienced with Full Stack Developer (React and FastAPI), Algorithm & Data, Computer Vision, Machine Learning.
- Programming languages: Python (4 years), JavaScript (4 years).
- Languages: Vietnamese (Native Speaker), English (Professional User).